couponrefund.com 2008-12-18

# Coupon Refund Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment to Privacy

CouponRefund.com privacy policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to providing you quality coupons and deals while maintaining integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. This policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide us and to assist you in making informed decisions about using this sites coupons and deals.

## What information do we collect?

Email address: You may provide your email address for our coupon newsletter that will be used for the sole purpose of providing you with the latest deals and offers from our partners. Please be assured that your email information will never be sold or distributed without your consent.

Cookies and web logs: Similar to other commercial web sites, our site utilizes a common standard known as “cookies” and web server logs to collect information about how our site is used by our guests. Cookies are a feature of your browser that contain bits of information that help personalize your web experience. You may always opt out of cookie collection by turning them off in your internet browsers settings. Cookies and web logs may track the following information: time of visit, time spent at our site, which pages were viewed, and the sites visited just before and just after our site. This information is not contain any personal information about you and is collected on an aggregate basis.

Choice / Opt Out Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may always opt out by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter. 

## Links 

Our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the practices, policies, or content of such sites and encourage our users to review the individual policies therein. 

## **Sharing anonymous information with Third Parties**

We may disclose anonymous web traffic statistics with our third parties and advertisers, but this will be done on an aggregate basis and never contain any personal information. 

**Legal Information Disclosure**

We may disclose information when legally required by law. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we change any portion of this policy in the ongoing development of our Web site, these changes will be posted to our homepage. Under the circumstance that any change is made to the collection or distribution of personal information, we will notify you via email. However, we will use any information you provide (namely your email) under the privacy policy under which it was collected. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at [feedback@couponrefund.com](mailto:feedback@couponrefund.com)
